{
  "questions": [
    {
      "qid": "p1u1-a1",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Good morning",
        "good afternoon",
        "good night"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Good afternoon"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u1-a2",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Good morning",
        "good afternoon",
        "goodbye"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Good morning"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u1-a3",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Principal",
        "friend",
        "teacher"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Teacher"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u1-a4",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Greek",
        "greet",
        "greed"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Greet"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u1-a5",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Moniter",
        "monitor",
        "moniker"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Monitor"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u1-a6",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Schoolmate",
        "classroom",
        "classmate"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Classmate"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u1-a7",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Gardener",
        "gadener",
        "gardenor"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Gardener"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u1-a8",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Hello",
        "hallo",
        "hullo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Hello"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u1-a9",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "freind",
        "fried",
        "friend"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Friend"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u1-a10",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Good morning",
        "good afternoon",
        "goodbye"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Goodbye"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u1-a11",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Janitor",
        "lender",
        "leader"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Leader"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u1-a12",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Princes",
        "principle",
        "princess"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Principal"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u1-a13",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Monitor",
        "driver",
        "janitor"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Driver"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u1-a14",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Cockroach",
        "coach",
        "couch"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Coach"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u1-a15",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Library",
        "libraries",
        "librarian"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Librarian"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u1-a16",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "English",
        "Chinese",
        "maths"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "English"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u1-a17",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "English",
        "Chinese",
        "maths"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Chinese"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u1-a18",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Leader",
        "driver",
        "janitor"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Janitor"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u1-a19",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Students",
        "student",
        "study"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Student"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u1-a20",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Prefect",
        "perfect",
        "principal"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Prefect"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u5-e1",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "I have black and white fur, and I love to eat bamboo.",
      "answers": [
        "Zebra",
        "Tiger",
        "Panda"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Panda"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u5-e2",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "I have a long nose that can pick up things.",
      "answers": [
        "Elephant",
        "Giraffe",
        "Rabbit"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Elephant"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u5-e3",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "My ears are so long, they almost touch the ground.",
      "answers": [
        "Rabbit",
        "Monkey",
        "Giraffe"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Rabbit"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u5-e4",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "I have a long neck. I can touch the leaves.",
      "answers": [
        "Elephant",
        "Giraffe",
        "Monkey"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u5-e5",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "I'm the king of the jungle. I have a loud roar.",
      "answers": [
        "Hippo",
        "Snake",
        "Lion"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Lion"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u5-e6",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "I have a round tummy and a short tail. My thick brown fur keeps me warm.",
      "answers": [
        "Panda",
        "Bear",
        "Hippo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Bear"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u5-e7",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "I am long. I have no legs and I slide.",
      "answers": [
        "Giraffe",
        "Tiger",
        "Snake"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Snake"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u5-e8",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "I have black and white stripes. I run on the grass.",
      "answers": [
        "Zebra",
        "Tiger",
        "Panda"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Zebra"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u5-e9",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "I have a long tail and I swing from tree to tree.",
      "answers": [
        "Rabbit",
        "Monkey",
        "Giraffe"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Monkey"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u5-e10",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "I am gray in color. I live near the river.",
      "answers": [
        "Tiger",
        "Crocodile",
        "Hippo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Hippo"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u1-c1",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Consern",
        "Concern",
        "Conxern",
        "Conncern"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Concern"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u1-c2",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Purform",
        "Perfune",
        "Parform",
        "Perform"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Perform"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u1-c3",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Aed",
        "Ald",
        "Aad",
        "Aid"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Aid"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u1-c4",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Sponser",
        "Sponcer",
        "Sponsar",
        "Sponsor"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Sponsor"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u1-c5",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Prepare",
        "Preepare",
        "Prep",
        "Prepair"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Prepare"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u1-c6",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Donate",
        "Donut",
        "Donute",
        "Danube"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Donate"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u1-c7",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Volanteer",
        "Volantis",
        "Volunteer",
        "Volume"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Volunteer"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u1-c8",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Assist",
        "Assixt",
        "Ascist",
        "Azziz"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Assist"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u1-c9",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Walkathon",
        "Talkathon",
        "Speakathon",
        "Sleepathon"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Walkathon"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u1-c10",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Gift",
        "Givt",
        "Gipht",
        "Grift"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Gift"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u1-c11",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Charrity",
        "Chairity",
        "Charety",
        "Charity"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Charity"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u1-c12",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Suppose",
        "Suport",
        "Subport",
        "Support"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Support"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u1-c13",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Reffle",
        "Roffle",
        "Raffle",
        "Riffle"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Raffle"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u1-c14",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Adipt",
        "Adoph",
        "Adorpt",
        "Adopt"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Adopt"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u1-c15",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Abandon",
        "Abanddon",
        "Abaddon",
        "Aband"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Abandon"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u1-c16",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Honeless",
        "Homeless",
        "Whomeless",
        "Homless"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Homeless"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u1-c17",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Organaize",
        "Org",
        "Organize",
        "Orgenize"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Organize"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u1-c18",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Fand",
        "Faund",
        "Fiund",
        "Fund"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Fund"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u1-c19",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Aelderly",
        "Alderly",
        "Ilderly",
        "Elderly"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Elderly"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u1-c20",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Colect",
        "Collect",
        "Collekt",
        "Corlect"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Collect"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u6-c1",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "umbrella",
        "skirt",
        "cheongsam",
        "robe"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "cheongsam"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u6-c2",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "poncho",
        "towel",
        "rug",
        "handkerchief"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "poncho"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u6-c3",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "kaiser",
        "kimono",
        "komodo",
        "katana"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kimono"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u6-c4",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "skirt",
        "kilt",
        "dress",
        "garter"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kilt"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u6-c5",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "hijab",
        "headband",
        "scarf",
        "hat"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hijab"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u6-c6",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "V-neck",
        "tank top",
        "T-shirt",
        "changshan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "changshan"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u6-c7",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "African drum",
        "American drum",
        "Asian drum",
        "Australian drum"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "African drum"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u6-c8",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "stamper",
        "simba",
        "timber",
        "samba"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "samba"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u6-c9",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "abs dance",
        "belly dance",
        "tummy dance",
        "stomach dance"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "belly dance"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u6-c10",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "haka",
        "hark",
        "hike",
        "hokum"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "haka"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u6-c11",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "Chinese opera",
        "Italian opera",
        "Spanish opera",
        "Flemish opera"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Chinese opera"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u6-c12",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "salsa sauce",
        "salsa dance",
        "salsa dip",
        "salsa chips"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "salsa dance"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u6-c13",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "jacuzzi",
        "gas",
        "jams",
        "jazz"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "jazz"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u6-c14",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "mochi",
        "kimchi",
        "sushi",
        "sashimi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "kimchi"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u6-c15",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "arm wrestling",
        "Greek wrestling",
        "sumo-wrestling",
        "WWE wrestling"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "sumo-wrestling"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u6-c16",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "cruises",
        "cuisines",
        "karmas",
        "corndogs"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "cuisines"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u6-c17",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "languages",
        "languishes",
        "lampreys",
        "lunges"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "languages"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u6-c18",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "releggings",
        "relics",
        "religieuse",
        "religions"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "religions"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u6-c19",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "customary",
        "costumes",
        "customs",
        "costs"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "costumes"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p6u6-c20",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "transportations",
        "traditions",
        "transitions",
        "trepidations"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "traditions"
    }
  ]

}